<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tai_WellnessApp</string>
    <string name="meditation">Meditation</string>
    <string name="healthy_recipes">Healthy Recipes</string>
    <string name="hydration_alert">Hydration Alert</string>
    <string name="start_exercise">Start Exercise</string>
    <string name="weekly_goal">Weekly Goal</string>
    <string name="daily_motivations">Daily Motivation</string>
    <string name="nutrition_advicetle">Nutrition Advice</string>
    <string name="check_progressive">Check Progress</string>
    <string name="nutrition_advice">
        Nutrition Advice\n\n1.
        Fruit Salad\nA mix of fresh fruits like bananas, apples, and oranges.\n\n2.
        Grilled Chicken\nLow-fat grilled chicken served with vegetables.\n\n3.
        Vegetable Stir Fry\nCarrots, broccoli, and peppers cooked lightly.\n\n4.
        Oatmeal Breakfast\nOats with milk and fruits.\n\n5.
        Avocado Toast\nWhole grain bread topped with avocado.\n\n6.
        Boiled Eggs\nRich in protein and easy to prepare.\n\n7.
        Smoothie Bowl\nBlended fruits with yogurt and nuts.\n\n8.
        Brown Rice and Beans\nHealthy and full of fiber.\n\n9.
        Baked Fish\nFish baked with lemon and spices.\n\n10.
        Greek Yogurt with Honey\nGood for digestion and very nutritious.
    </string>
    <string name="meditation_content">
        Meditation Content\n\n1.
        Mindful Breathing\nFocus on your breath, inhaling and exhaling slowly to calm your mind.\n\n2.
        Body Scan Meditation\nGently bring awareness to each part of your body from head to toe.\n\n3.
        Guided Visualization\nImagine a peaceful place like a beach or forest to relax your thoughts.\n\n4.
        Loving-Kindness Meditation\nSilently repeat phrases wishing well-being for yourself and others.\n\n5.
        Mantra Meditation\nRepeat a calming word or phrase to maintain focus and clarity.\n\n6.
        Walking Meditation\nWalk slowly and focus on each step and movement of your body.\n\n7.
        Gratitude Meditation\nReflect on things you are thankful for to cultivate positivity.\n\n8.
        Silent Sitting\nSit quietly and observe your thoughts without judgment.\n\n9.
        Chakra Meditation\nFocus on different energy centers in your body for balance.\n\n10.
        Progressive Relaxation\nTense and relax each muscle group to release physical stress.
    </string>

    <string name="exercise_content">
        Start Exercise\n\n1.
        Warm-Up Stretch\nGently stretch your muscles to prepare your body for activity.\n\n2.
        Jumping Jacks\nA simple full-body exercise to increase heart rate.\n\n3.
        Bodyweight Squats\nStrengthen your legs and improve balance.\n\n4.
        Push-Ups\nBuild upper body strength using your own weight.\n\n5.
        Plank Hold\nEngage your core and improve stability.\n\n6.
        Lunges\nWork your legs and improve coordination.\n\n7.
        High Knees\nBoost cardio and activate lower body muscles.\n\n8.
        Mountain Climbers\nA great full-body workout for strength and endurance.\n\n9.
        Cool Down Stretch\nSlowly stretch to relax muscles after exercise.\n\n10.
        Deep Breathing\nCalm your body and restore normal breathing.
    </string>
    <string name="check_progress">
       Check Progress

       Fruit Mix Bowl – A refreshing combination of seasonal fruits that provides natural sugars and vitamins.
       Lean Grilled Chicken – Lightly seasoned chicken cooked without excess oil, perfect for muscle health.
       Sautéed Vegetables – A colorful mix of lightly cooked veggies that retain nutrients and flavor.
       Warm Oats Meal – A filling breakfast made with oats, offering long-lasting energy throughout the day.
       Avocado Bread Slice – Crunchy whole grain bread layered with creamy avocado for healthy fats.
       Hard-Boiled Eggs – Simple protein-rich eggs that help keep you full and energized.
       Creamy Fruit Blend – A thick mix of blended fruits, yogurt, and crunchy toppings for added texture.
       Whole Grain Rice and Legumes – A balanced dish packed with fiber and plant-based protein.☐ Oven-Cooked Fish – Gently baked fish infused with herbs for a heart-friendly meal.
       Yogurt with Natural Sweetness – Smooth yogurt paired with a touch of honey to support gut health.
    </string>
    <string name="daily_motivation">
        Daily Motivation



    </string>


</resources>