<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tai_WellnessApp</string>
    <string name="meditation">Meditation</string>
    <string name="healthy_recipes">Healthy Recipes</string>
    <string name="hydration_alert">Hydration Alert</string>
    <string name="start_exercise">Start Exercise</string>
    <string name="weekly_goal">Weekly Goal</string>
    <string name="daily_motivations">Daily Motivation</string>
    <string name="nutrition_advicetle">Nutrition Advice</string>
    <string name="check_progressive">Check Progress</string>
    <string name="healthyrecipecnt">
        Healthy Recipe\n\n1.
        Fruit Salad\nA mix of fresh fruits like bananas, apples, and oranges.\n\n2.
        Grilled Chicken\nLow-fat grilled chicken served with vegetables.\n\n3.
        Vegetable Stir Fry\nCarrots, broccoli, and peppers cooked lightly.\n\n4.
        Oatmeal Breakfast\nOats with milk and fruits.\n\n5.
        Avocado Toast\nWhole grain bread topped with avocado.\n\n6.
        Boiled Eggs\nRich in protein and easy to prepare.\n\n7.
        Smoothie Bowl\nBlended fruits with yogurt and nuts.\n\n8.
        Brown Rice and Beans\nHealthy and full of fiber.\n\n9.
        Baked Fish\nFish baked with lemon and spices.\n\n10.
        Greek Yogurt with Honey\nGood for digestion and very nutritious.
    </string>
    <string name="nutrition_advice">
        Nutrition Advice\n\n1.
        Fruit Salad\nA mix of fresh fruits like bananas, apples, and oranges.\n\n2.
        Grilled Chicken\nLow-fat grilled chicken served with vegetables.\n\n3.
        Vegetable Stir Fry\nCarrots, broccoli, and peppers cooked lightly.\n\n4.
        Oatmeal Breakfast\nOats with milk and fruits.\n\n5.
        Avocado Toast\nWhole grain bread topped with avocado.\n\n6.
        Boiled Eggs\nRich in protein and easy to prepare.\n\n7.
        Smoothie Bowl\nBlended fruits with yogurt and nuts.\n\n8.
        Brown Rice and Beans\nHealthy and full of fiber.\n\n9.
        Baked Fish\nFish baked with lemon and spices.\n\n10.
        Greek Yogurt with Honey\nGood for digestion and very nutritious.
    </string>
    <string name="meditation_content">
        Meditation Content\n\n1.
        Mindful Breathing\nFocus on your breath, inhaling and exhaling slowly to calm your mind.\n\n2.
        Body Scan Meditation\nGently bring awareness to each part of your body from head to toe.\n\n3.
        Guided Visualization\nImagine a peaceful place like a beach or forest to relax your thoughts.\n\n4.
        Loving-Kindness Meditation\nSilently repeat phrases wishing well-being for yourself and others.\n\n5.
        Mantra Meditation\nRepeat a calming word or phrase to maintain focus and clarity.\n\n6.
        Walking Meditation\nWalk slowly and focus on each step and movement of your body.\n\n7.
        Gratitude Meditation\nReflect on things you are thankful for to cultivate positivity.\n\n8.
        Silent Sitting\nSit quietly and observe your thoughts without judgment.\n\n9.
        Chakra Meditation\nFocus on different energy centers in your body for balance.\n\n10.
        Progressive Relaxation\nTense and relax each muscle group to release physical stress.
    </string>

    <string name="exercise_content">
        Start Exercise\n\n1.
        Warm-Up Stretch\nGently stretch your muscles to prepare your body for activity.\n\n2.
        Jumping Jacks\nA simple full-body exercise to increase heart rate.\n\n3.
        Bodyweight Squats\nStrengthen your legs and improve balance.\n\n4.
        Push-Ups\nBuild upper body strength using your own weight.\n\n5.
        Plank Hold\nEngage your core and improve stability.\n\n6.
        Lunges\nWork your legs and improve coordination.\n\n7.
        High Knees\nBoost cardio and activate lower body muscles.\n\n8.
        Mountain Climbers\nA great full-body workout for strength and endurance.\n\n9.
        Cool Down Stretch\nSlowly stretch to relax muscles after exercise.\n\n10.
        Deep Breathing\nCalm your body and restore normal breathing.
    </string>
    <string name="check_progress">
       Check Progress

       Fruit Mix Bowl – A refreshing combination of seasonal fruits that provides natural sugars and vitamins.
       Lean Grilled Chicken – Lightly seasoned chicken cooked without excess oil, perfect for muscle health.
       Sautéed Vegetables – A colorful mix of lightly cooked veggies that retain nutrients and flavor.
       Warm Oats Meal – A filling breakfast made with oats, offering long-lasting energy throughout the day.
       Avocado Bread Slice – Crunchy whole grain bread layered with creamy avocado for healthy fats.
       Hard-Boiled Eggs – Simple protein-rich eggs that help keep you full and energized.
       Creamy Fruit Blend – A thick mix of blended fruits, yogurt, and crunchy toppings for added texture.
       Whole Grain Rice and Legumes – A balanced dish packed with fiber and plant-based protein.☐ Oven-Cooked Fish – Gently baked fish infused with herbs for a heart-friendly meal.
       Yogurt with Natural Sweetness – Smooth yogurt paired with a touch of honey to support gut health.
    </string>
    <string name="daily_motivation">
        Daily Motivation
    </string>

    <string name="hydration_content">
        Start Hydration\n\n1.
        Morning Glass\nDrink a glass of water immediately after waking up to rehydrate.\n\n2.
        Carry a Bottle\nKeep a reusable water bottle with you throughout the day.\n\n3.
        Sip Regularly\nTake small, frequent sips instead of gulping large amounts.\n\n4.
        Flavor Naturally\nAdd lemon, cucumber, or mint to make water more refreshing.\n\n5.
        Eat Your Water\nConsume hydrating foods like watermelon, celery, and cucumber.\n\n6.
        Pre-Meal Glass\nDrink water 30 minutes before meals to aid digestion.\n\n7.
        Post-Activity Refill\nReplenish fluids lost through sweat after any physical activity.\n\n8.
        Monitor Color\nCheck that your urine is pale yellow, a sign of good hydration.\n\n9.
        Set Reminders\nUse an app or alarm to remind you to drink at regular intervals.\n\n10.
        Evening Limit\nTaper off fluid intake before bed to ensure restful sleep.
    </string>

    <string name="check_progress_content">
        Weekly Progress\n\n1.
        Set Weekly Goals\nDefine clear and achievable fitness or hydration goals for the week.\n\n2.
        Track Daily Activity\nRecord your workouts, steps, or water intake each day.\n\n3.
        Monitor Consistency\nCheck how often you stick to your routine throughout the week.\n\n4.
        Measure Performance\nNote improvements in strength, endurance, or energy levels.\n\n5.
        Check Body Signals\nPay attention to how your body feels—energy, soreness, and recovery.\n\n6.
        Review Nutrition\nEvaluate your eating habits and hydration levels.\n\n7.
        Celebrate Wins\nAcknowledge small achievements to stay motivated.\n\n8.
        Identify Challenges\nRecognize obstacles that affected your progress.\n\n9.
        Adjust Plan\nModify your routine based on what worked or didn’t.\n\n10.
        Prepare Next Week\nSet new goals and plan ahead for continued progress.
    </string>

    <string name="start_exercise_content">
        Start Exercise  Check Progress\n\n1.
        Warm-Up First\nBegin with light stretches to prepare your body.\n\n2.
        Start Small\nChoose simple exercises to build consistency.\n\n3.
        Follow Routine\nStick to a structured workout plan.\n\n4.
        Track Reps\nCount repetitions and sets during each exercise.\n\n5.
        Time Your Workout\nMonitor how long you exercise each session.\n\n6.
        Note Difficulty\nRecord how challenging each workout feels.\n\n7.
        Stay Consistent\nExercise regularly to build momentum.\n\n8.
        Compare Progress\nCheck improvements over time in strength and stamina.\n\n9.
        Adjust Intensity\nIncrease difficulty gradually as you improve.\n\n10.
        Reflect  Improve\nReview your progress and refine your routine.
    </string>
    <string name="healthy_recipes_content">
        Healthy Recipes\n\n1.
        Start Simple\nChoose easy recipes with few ingredients to build consistency.\n\n2.
        Use Fresh Ingredients\nIncorporate fresh fruits, vegetables, and whole foods.\n\n3.
        Balance Your Plate\nInclude protein, healthy fats, and complex carbohydrates.\n\n4.
        Control Portions\nServe appropriate portions to avoid overeating.\n\n5.
        Cook at Home\nPrepare meals at home to control ingredients and nutrition.\n\n6.
        Limit Processed Foods\nReduce intake of packaged and highly processed items.\n\n7.
        Healthy Cooking Methods\nUse grilling, steaming, or baking instead of frying.\n\n8.
        Stay Hydrated\nPair meals with water instead of sugary drinks.\n\n9.
        Plan Meals\nPrepare a weekly meal plan to stay on track.\n\n10.
        Enjoy Mindfully\nEat slowly and appreciate your meals for better digestion.
    </string>
    <string name="daily_motivation_content">
        Daily Motivation\n\n1.
        Start with Gratitude\nBegin your day by appreciating what you have.\n\n2.
        Set Daily Goals\nDefine small, achievable goals for the day.\n\n3.
        Positive Mindset\nFocus on what can go right instead of what can go wrong.\n\n4.
        Take Action\nStart even if you don’t feel ready—progress comes from doing.\n\n5.
        Stay Consistent\nSmall efforts every day lead to big results.\n\n6.
        Embrace Challenges\nView obstacles as opportunities to grow.\n\n7.
        Learn Daily\nGain something new each day, no matter how small.\n\n8.
        Avoid Negativity\nLimit exposure to negative thoughts and influences.\n\n9.
        Reflect on Progress\nLook back at what you’ve achieved, not just what’s left.\n\n10.
        End with Positivity\nFinish your day with a positive thought or reflection.
    </string>


</resources>